Guide to the Roy Radner Papers, 1951-2014 RL.11298
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Correspondence, 1959-2014; 2
  This series contains Roy Radner's correspondence, from 1959 up until 2014. Files are sorted by individuals' names. Roughly half the files include an actual correspondence between Radner and the individual named on the file, while the other half contains materials about the individual named on the file (mostly recommendation letters, but also papers, Ph.D. dissertations, CVs). There is also a set of personal files -- the names of which all start by "Radner, Roy".
  Conditions Governing Access
  This series is closed until 2050 due to the high concentration of personnel and tenure review/recommendation letters within these files.
  - Blume, Larry, 1981-2007 (Box 11)
  - Bolton, P., 2005 (Box 11)
  - Bose, Satyajit, 2006 (Box 11)
  - Bray, Margaret, 1981-1984 (Box 11)
  - Brock, William A., 1979-1983 (Box 11)
  - Broman, Elizabeth, 1985-1988; 2 folders (Box 12)
  - Brown, Alexander, 1993-1995 and undated (Box 12)
  - Bryant, John, 1990-1996 (Box 12)
  - Buchanan, Bruce, 2004-2009 (Box 12)
  - Buttrick, John, 1961-1998 and undated (Box 12)
  - C, 1979-2006 (Box 12)
  - Cambridge University Press, 1979-1998 (Box 12)
  - Campo Rembado, Miguel Angel, 2001-2006; 2 folders (Box 12)
  - Carnegie-Mellon University, 1979 and undated (Box 12)
  - Chen, Fei, 1996-2000 and undated; 2 folders (Box 12)
  - Chen, Sarah, 2012-2013; 2 folders (Box 12)
  - Chichilnisky, Graciela, 1978-1996 and undated (Box 12)
  - Chipman, John S., Undated (Box 12)
  - Cho, In-Koo, 1994-1997 (Box 12)
  - Churchill College, 1982-1993 (Box 12)
  - Cleveland, Mary M. (Polly Roberts), 1984-1994 (Box 12)
  - Cohen, Susan I., 1981 (Box 12)
  - Cole, Jonathan, 2006 (Box 12)
  - Conley, Caryn, 2006 and undated (Box 12)
  - Contemporary Economic Policy, 1998 (Box 12)
  - Cooley, Thomas, 2009 (Box 12)
  - Cornell University, 1977-1980 (Box 12)
  - D, 1978-2001 (Box 12)
  - Daly, George (Dean, Stern), 1997-2001 (Box 12)
  - Dana, Rose-Anne, 1973-2007 (Box 12)
  - Dasgupta, Partha, 1980-1998 (Box 12)
  - Day, Richard H., 1983-2007 (Box 12)
  - Debreu, Gerard, 1991-2001 and undated; 2 folders (Box 12)
  - Decision and Organization Royalties, 1976-1977 (Box 12)
  - Dehez, Pierre, 2005 (Box 12)
  - Dellarocas, Chrysanthos, 2000-2001 and undated (Box 12)
  - Dewan, Sanjeev, 2001 (Box 12)
  - Dewatriport, M., 2005 (Box 12)
  - Dhar, Vasant, 2006-2008 (Box 12)
  - Diamant, Adam, Undated (Box 12)
  - Ding, 2008 (Box 12)
  - Doucet, Joseph A., 1990-1992 (Box 12)
  - Dow, Gregory, 1988-1995 (Box 12)
  - Dow, James, 1993-1996 (Box 12)
  - Drozdova, Katya, 2004-2009; 7 folders (Box 12)
  - Duncan, Gregory, 1975-2009 (Box 12)
  - Dutta, Prajit K., 1985-2004 and undated; 2 folders (Box 13)
  - Dynkin, E. B., 1972-1985 (Box 13)
  - E, 1979-1998 (Box 13)
  - Eagle, David, 2004 (Box 13)
  - Easly, David, 1980-1987 (Box 13)
  - Econometric Society, 1977-2010; 2 folders (Box 13)
  - Econometrica, 1998 (Box 13)
  - Economic Journal - Controversy, 1995 (Box 13)
  - Economides, Nicholas S., 1981-2010; 6 folders (Box 13)
  - El-Gamal, Mahmoud, 1991-1994 and undated (Box 13)
  - Eliasson, G., 1986-1994 and undated (Box 13)
  - Environmental Studies NYU College of Arts and Sciences, 2010 (Box 13)
  - Erickson, Richard, 1977-1984 (Box 13)
  - European Economic Review, 1997-1998 (Box 13)
  - F, 1978-1999 (Box 13)
  - Fang, Chi-Yu, 1990 (Box 13)
  - Fluck, 1990-1994 (Box 13)
  - Friedman, Howard, Undated (Box 13)
  - Friedman, J. W., 1978-1986 (Box 13)
  - Futia, Carl A., Undated (Box 13)
  - G, 1968-2007 (Box 13)
  - Gale, Douglas, 1978-1995 (Box 13)
  - Garcia, Andres E., 1999 (Box 13)
  - Geanakoplos, John, 1981-2001 and undated (Box 13)
  - Gerard-Varet, L. A., 1992-1996 and undated (Box 13)
  - Ghose, Anindya, 2004; 2 folders (Box 13)
  - Gifford, Sharon, 1984-1999 and undated (Box 13)
  - Gonen, Rica, 2007 and undated (Box 13)
  - Gorman, W. M., 1975-1999 (Box 13)
  - Gottinger, Hans W., 1998-2007 (Box 13)
  - Govindan, Shrihari, 1991-1993 (Box 13)
  - Graham, R. L., 1985 (Box 13)
  - Grandmont, Jean-Michel, 1980-1991 (Box 13)
  - Grandori, Anna, 2001 and undated (Box 13)
  - Green, Edward J., 1985 (Box 13)
  - Green, J., 1979-1989 (Box 13)
  - Gresik, Thomas, 1990-1996 (Box 13)
  - Groves, Theodore, 1971-2000 (Box 13)
  - H, 1978-2007 (Box 13)
  - Hahn, F., 1970-1995 (Box 13)
  - Hahn, F. - AER, 1996-1998 (Box 13)
    About a problem in the publication process of a paper by Arrow and Hahn
  - Hansmann, Henry, 1999 (Box 13)
  - Harsanyi, John Charles, 1984-1986 (Box 13)
  - Harvard - Economics Department, 1977-1978 (Box 13)
  - Harvard University - Econ. 2181, Spring 1978, 1977-1978 (Box 13)
  - Heal, Geoffrey, 2005 (Box 14)
  - Henry, Peter Blair, 2009-2013 (Box 14)
  - Hess, J., 1978-1988 (Box 14)
  - Hildenbrand, Werner, 1975-1999 (Box 14)
  - Hitt, Lorin Moultrie, 2001 (Box 14)
  - Honors Program Applicants, 2009 (Box 14)
  - Huang, Kei-Wei, 1998-2007 and undated; 5 folders (Box 14)
  - Humor, 1988 and undated (Box 14)
  - Huynh, H. L., 1994-2000 and undated; 2 folders (Box 14)
  - Hurwicz, L., 1959-2008; 2 folders (Box 14)
  - Hurwicz Volumes, 1980-1982 (Box 14)
  - Hussain, Bilal, 2008 (Box 14)
  - I, 1978-1997 (Box 14)
  - Ichiishi, Tatsuro, 1976-2000 and undated; 2 folders (Box 14)
  - IIASA - Intern. Institute For Applied Systems Analysis, 1977-1978 and undated (Box 14)
  - IMSSS - Summer, 1980 (Box 14)
  - IMSSS Summer Seminar - Kurz, Mordecai, 1978 (Box 14)
  - Inaba, Fred, 1973-1980 (Box 14)
  - Information Economy, 1982-1985 and undated (Box 14)
  - Information Systems Frontiers, 1997-2000 and undated; 3 folders (Box 14)
  - International Herbert A. Simon Society, 2009-2010 (Box 14)
  - Ipeirotis, Panos, 2004-2005; 2 folders (Box 14)
  - J, 1979-2012 (Box 14)
  - Jain, Neelam, 1996-1997 (Box 14)
  - Jasso, Guillermina, 2005 (Box 14)
  - JeanJean, Patrick, 1971-1975 (Box 14)
  - Jin, Bing, 2004-2007 (Box 14)
  - Jordan, James, 1977-1997 (Box 14)
  - Journal of Accounting, Auditing, Finance, 1986 (Box 14)
  - Journal of Economic Behavior and Organization, 1993 (Box 14)
  - Journal of Economic Theory, 2002 (Box 14)
  - Journal of Mathematical Economics, 1996-1998 (Box 14)
  - K, 1979-2007 (Box 14)
  - Kalai, E., 1987-2001 (Box 14)
  - Kamlet, Mark, 1977-1990 (Box 14)
  - Karp, Sari, 1999 (Box 14)
  - Katsamakas, Evangelos, 2003-2004 (Box 14)
  - Kerr, C., 1980-2001 (Box 14)
  - Keser, Claudia, Undated (Box 14)
  - King, A., 1999 (Box 14)
  - Klaes, Matthias, 1999-2000; 2 folders (Box 14)
  - Klein, L. R., 1963-1983 (Box 14)
  - Koonin, Steve, 2012 (Box 14)
  - Koopmans, T. C., 1974-1988 (Box 14)
  - Kornai, Janos, 1968-1983 (Box 14)
  - Kornhauser, Lewis, 1977-1988 (Box 14)
  - Kreps, D. M., 1977-1987 (Box 14)
  - Krishnan, M. S., 2005 (Box 14)
  - Kruskal, William, 1977-1978 (Box 14)
  - Kuh, C. V. "Education and Productivity", 1970-1998 (Box 14)
  - L, 1978-1999 (Box 15)
  - Lagunoff, Roger, 1991-1998 (Box 15)
  - Lambert-Mogiliansky, Ariane, 1997-2010 (Box 15)
  - Larson, Carole, 2008-2009 (Box 15)
  - Lau, Nancy, 2005 (Box 15)
  - Laval University, 1983-1984 (Box 15)
  - Ledyard, John O., 1978-1996 (Box 15)
  - Leininger, Wolfgang, 1986-1988 and undated (Box 15)
  - Light, Andrew, 2003-2004 (Box 15)
  - Linhart, P. B., 1988-1995 (Box 15)
  - Lizzeri, Ariel, Undated (Box 15)
  - Lopomo, G., 1998-2004 (Box 15)
  - M, 1987-2006 and undated (Box 15)
  - Majumdar, Mukul K., 1990-1997 (Box 15)
  - Majumdar Volume, 2003 (Box 15)
  - Malinvaud, Edmond, 1991-2006 (Box 15)
  - Mallilck, Soumitra Kumar, 2007 (Box 15)
  - Mantena, Ravindra N., 2002-2004 (Box 15)
  - March, James G., 2001 (Box 15)
  - Martos, Bela, 1985 (Box 15)
  - Marschak, Thomas, 1975-1995 (Box 15)
  - Mas-Collell, Andreu, 1971-1993 (Box 15)
  - Maskin, E. S., 1980-1988 (Box 15)
  - McFadden, D., 1969-1997 (Box 15)
  - McKenzie, L. W., 1967-2001 (Box 15)
  - Meagher, K., 1995-1998 (Box 15)
  - Merchant, Doug, 1984-1991 and undated (Box 15)
  - Meurer Michael, J., 1991-1997 (Box 15)
  - Milgram, P., 1980-1987 (Box 15)
  - Miller, G. L., 1990-1995 (Box 15)
  - Mills, Julia, Undated (Box 15)
  - Minnesota Univ. - Inst. for mathematics and its applications, 1982-1984 (Box 15)
  - Minnesota Univ. Press - Decision and Organization, 1983-1984 (Box 15)
  - Miraftab, Nima, 2008-2010 (Box 15)
  - MIT Press, 1986-1994 (Box 15)
  - Mityagin, Boris, 1987-1989 and undated (Box 15)
  - Mody, Ashoka, 1986 (Box 15)
  - Mortensen, Mark, 2004 (Box 15)
  - Moulin, Herve, 1987-1997 (Box 15)
  - Muthoo, Abhinay, 1994-1996 (Box 15)
  - Myerson, Roger B., 1981-1988 (Box 15)
  - N, 1977-1998 (Box 15)
  - Nadiri, M. Ishaq, 1993 (Box 15)
  - National Bureau of Economic Research, 1992-1994 and undated (Box 15)
  - National Science Foundation - General, 1978-1991 (Box 15)
  - NCR Trust in Cyberspace, 1997-1998 and undated (Box 15)
  - NSF Proposal, 2009 (Box 15)
  - Nayyar, P., 2005 (Box 15)
  - Neuefeind, Wilhelm, 1984-1999 (Box 15)
  - Newlon, Daniel H., 1981 (Box 15)
  - New York University - Administration; 1983- 95 (Box 15)
  - Nobel Prize, 1979-1995 (Box 15)
  - Nocke, Volker, Undated (Box 15)
  - North-Holland Publishing Company, 1980-1987 (Box 15)
  - NYU Library, 1998 (Box 15)
  - O, 1975-1998 (Box 15)
  - Oestreicher-Singer, Gal, 2004-2005 (Box 15)
  - Oxford, 1966 (Box 15)
  - Ok, Effe A., 1997 (Box 15)
  - Ohlson, James, 1998 (Box 15)
  - P, 1978-2011 (Box 16)
  - Palgrave, 2007 (Box 16)
  - Papadimitrakopoulos, George, 2011 (Box 16)
  - Park, Sangwon, 2003; 2 folders (Box 16)
  - Peleg, Bezalel, 1972-1977 (Box 16)
  - Penzias, A. A., 1983-1984 and undated; 2 folders (Box 16)
  - Polemarchakis, Heraklis, 1979-1989 (Box 16)
  - Prabhakar, Akila, 2009 (Box 16)
  - Prasad, Kislaya, 1994-2003 and undated (Box 16)
  - Prat, Andrea, 2005 (Box 16)
  - Princeton University, 1992-1994 (Box 16)
  - Provost, Foster, 2006 (Box 16)
  - Q, 1995 (Box 16)
  - R, 1990-2006 (Box 16)
  - Radner, Roy - Administration, 1995-2009 (Box 16)
  - Radner, Roy - Articles by Franck Hahn, 1992 (Box 16)
    Only a reprint of Hahn's paper on Radner
  - Radner, Roy - Biographical Data, 1973-1978 (Box 16)
  - Radner, Roy - Biographical Material, 1983-2010 and undated (Box 16)
  - Radner, Roy - Decentralizacio es Erdekeltseg, Undated (Box 16)
    Only a reprint of a translation of a paper from Radner
  - Radner, Roy - Faculty Activity Reports, 1996-2014 (Box 16)
  - Radner, Roy - FAR 1/2011, 2010-2011 (Box 16)
  - Radner, Roy - FAR 1/25/09, 2009 (Box 16)
  - Radner, Roy - FAR 2012 (Box 16)
  - Radner, Roy - FAR 2012-2013 (Box 16)
  - Radner, Roy - FAR Jan 2005, 2005-2006 (Box 16)
  - Radner, Roy - Form 1, 1979-1995 and undated (Box 16)
  - Radner, Roy - Personal, 1959-1979; 2 folders (Box 16)
    File 2 contains correspondence with various famous economists, 1959-1965
  - Radner, Roy - Photo, Undated (Box 16)
    Contains a printed photo of Radner with its negative
  - Radner, Roy - Lists Plans, 1981-1996 (Box 16)
  - Radner, Roy - Memorabilia, 1989-1991 (Box 16)
  - Radner, Roy - Reviews, 1978-1980 (Box 16)
  - Radner, Roy - Sabbatical Fall 2009, 2008 (Box 16)
  - Radner, Roy - Senior Faculty Peer Review, 2003 (Box 16)
  - Radner, Roy - Senior Faculty Peer Review - 2002, 1998-2002 (Box 16)
  - Radunskaya, Amy, 1990-2007 (Box 16)
  - Raghubir, Priya, 2009 (Box 16)
  - Raj, Baldev, 1991 and undated (Box 16)
  - RAND, 1967-1975 (Box 16)
  - Reichelstein, Stefan J., 1990-2000 (Box 16)
  - Reiter, Stanley, 1977-2001 (Box 16)
  - Reiter Volume, 1990-1995 (Box 16)
  - Review of Accounting Studies, 1993-1994 (Box 16)
  - Reviews, 1999-2010 (Box 16)
  - Riley, John, 1979 (Box 16)
  - Riordan, Michael, 1997-1999; 2 folders (Box 16)
  - Rivlin, A., 1992-1993 and undated (Box 16)
  - Rob, Rafi, 1999-2006 (Box 16)
  - Rodriguez, Gustavo E., 1992-1998 (Box 16)
  - Rom, Merav, 2001 (Box 16)
  - Ronen, Joshua, 1984-2001 (Box 16)
  - Rosenthal, Robert W., 1978-2004; 2 folders (Box 16)
  - Roy, Santanu, 1998-2005 and undated; 3 folders (Box 17)
  - Rothschild, Michael, 1968-1989 and undated (Box 17)
  - Rubinstein, Ariel, 1980-2006 and undated (Box 17)
  - Rustichini, Aldo, 1987-2007 and undated (Box 17)
  - The Russel Sage Foundation, 1996-1999 (Box 17)
  - S, 1977-2003 and undated (Box 17)
  - Saar-Tsechansky, Maytal, 1997-2002 and undated (Box 17)
  - Saari, Donald G., 1989-1991 (Box 17)
  - Sadler, Evan, 2009-2014; 2 folders (Box 17)
  - Sankaranarayanan, Ramesh, 2002-2005; 2 folders (Box 17)
  - Scarf, H., 1967-1995 (Box 17)
  - The Scientist, 2001-2003 (Box 17)
  - Schargrodsky, Ernesto, 2007 (Box 17)
  - Scotchmer, Suzanne Andersen, 1994-1995 (Box 17)
  - Selten, Reinhard, 1975-1976 (Box 17)
  - Sentarskaya, Emiliya, 2011 (Box 17)
  - Sertel, Murat, 1993-2001 (Box 17)
  - Sevy, David, 1993-2002 and undated (Box 17)
  - Shapira, Zur, 1986-1999 (Box 17)
  - Shapley, Lloyd, 1977 (Box 17)
  - Sharkey, William W., 1993-1995 (Box 17)
  - Shell, Karl, 1975-1977 (Box 17)
  - Shepp, Larry, 2012 (Box 17)
  - Shima, Kenta, 2005 (Box 17)
  - Simon, Herbert, 2001 (Box 17)
    Contains only a booklet about Simon (obituary)
  - Simon Society, 2010-2012; 2 folders (Box 17)
  - Singh, Nirvikar, 2005 (Box 17)
  - Skianis, Vasileios, 2006 (Box 17)
  - Skreta, Vasiliki, 2007 (Box 17)
  - Smith, Vernon, 1986-1990 (Box 17)
  - Solow, Robert M., 1992-1994 (Box 17)
  - Sondermann, Dieter, 1977-1980 (Box 17)
  - Sonnenschein, Hugo, 1977-1999 (Box 17)
  - Soreide, Tina, 2003 (Box 17)
  - Spiewak, Monika - Honors Thesis Spring 2009 (Box 17)
  - Sproull, Lee, 2005 (Box 17)
  - Stern Dept Chairs Meeting, 2005 (Box 17)
  - Stimpson, Catherine, 2010 (Box 17)
  - Su, Ning - Recommendations, 2009 and undated (Box 17)
  - Sundararajan, Arun, 1996-2001 (Box 17)
  - T, 1979-2001 (Box 17)
  - Taylor, Sean, 2011 (Box 17)
  - Teitelbaum, Michael, 1991 (Box 17)
  - Tilburg, University, 1999 (Box 17)
  - Tesfatsion - Handbook, 2004 (Box 17)
  - Tobin, James, 1991 (Box 17)
  - Toman, Michael, 2004 (Box 17)
  - Trancik, Jessica, 2009 (Box 17)
  - Turner, Jon A., 2002-2005 (Box 17)
  - U, 1977-1999 (Box 17)
  - Unver, Utku M., 2004 (Box 17)
  - Uretsky, Mike, Undated (Box 17)
  - V, 1979-2008 (Box 18)
  - VanZandt, Timothy P., 1988-2009 (Box 18)
  - Vayanos, Dimitri, 2003 (Box 18)
  - Viard, Brian, 2005 (Box 18)
  - Vickrey, William, Undated (Box 18)
  - Vyssotsky, V.A., 1987-1984 (Box 18)
  - W, 1978-1999 (Box 18)
  - Wagner, Ulrich, 2007-2008 (Box 18)
  - Wang, Cecil, 2005-2007; 2 folders (Box 18)
  - Weber, Bruce, 1998-2002 (Box 18)
  - Weber, Elke U., 1999 (Box 18)
  - Weber, Thomas A., 2009-2010 (Box 18)
  - Weibull, Jorgen W., 1988-2009 (Box 18)
  - Weinberg, Alvin M., 1985-1987 (Box 18)
  - Wen, Zhona, 2001 (Box 18)
  - Who's Who in Science and Engineering, 2010 (Box 18)
  - Williams, Steven R., 1983-2002 (Box 18)
  - Williamson, Oliver E., 1988-1992 (Box 18)
  - Wilson, Robert, 1973-1986 (Box 18)
  - Winter, Sidney G., 1967-1994 (Box 18)
  - Wise, David, 1971-1987 (Box 18)
  - Wooders, John, 1996 (Box 18)
  - Wooders, Myrna, 1980-1997 (Box 18)
  - Woroch, Glenn, 1977-1999 (Box 18)
  - Wright, Margaret H., Undated (Box 18)
  - Wright, Robert F., 2001 (Box 18)
  - Xin, Mingdi, 2004-2012 and undated; 6 folders (Box 18)
  - Y, 1978-1993 (Box 18)
  - Yale University Press, 1974 (Box 18)
  - Yang, Shinkyu, 2000 (Box 18)
  - Yannelis, Nicholas C., 1991-1993 (Box 18)
  - Younes, Yves, 1984-1988 (Box 18)
  - Young, H. P., 1978-1986 (Box 18)
  - Young, Warren, 2010 (Box 18)
  - Z, 1979-2007 (Box 18)
  - Zajac, Edward E., 1981-2011 and undated; 2 folders (Box 18)
  - Zamir, Shmuel, 1999-2001 (Box 18)
  - Zilcha, Iztzhak, 1982-1996 (Box 18)
  - Mail-merge documents, 1977 (Digital-materials RL11298-SET-0001)
    Final mailing list for Radner's address change in 1997, with supporting mail-merge documents. Word 97 documents, 0.000117 gigabytes.
- Teaching, 1967-2012; 3
  This series contains materials related to Roy Radner's teaching activity. Half of it (i.e., a full box) is about the course "Microeconomics: Theory and Application (META)", taught at the Stern School (NYU) from 2000 up until 2012. The other half is about various courses (all microeconomics courses, mostly about the theory of the firm, and some notably as applied to environmental issues) taught at different institutions (though the bulk is largely at the Stern School from the late 1990s to the early 2010s). The different types of materials can be: syllabus, reading lists and packets, exercises with solutions, administrative documents, and a few notes taken for the preparation of courses.
  - Microeconomics: Theory and Application (META), 2000-2012 and undated; 91 folders (Box 19)
  - Mix of Notes for META and The Economy of Large Firms, 2000-2001 (Box 19)
  - The Economy of Large Firms, 1994-1997 and undated; 5 folders (Box 20)
  - Information and the Organization of the Firm, 1996-1997 and undated; 7 folders (Box 20)
  - Environmental Economics, 2005-2008; 7 folders (Box 20)
  - Business and the Environment, 2007-2012 and undated; 13 folders (Box 20)
  - Seminar on Experimental Economics, 1983-1986 (Box 20)
  - Strategic use of Incentives and Information: An Experimental Approach, 1997-1999 and undated; 7 folders (Box 20)
  - Statistics 169 - Dynamic Programming, 1973-1976; 4 folders (Box 20)
  - Notes on Constrained Optimization (Econ 202A), 1976 (Box 20)
  - Economics 201 and 207, 1973-1977 (Box 20)
  - The Economics of Engineering and Social Systems, 1969 (Box 20)
  - Teaching Notes - Varia, 1967-1971 (Box 20)
    Original file name: "Notes on Efficient Allocation and Growth"
- Research Activities, 1962-2014; 4
  This series include materials about various research activities conducted by Roy Radner, e.g., seminars, workshops, study groups, lectures, notes from research meetings etc. The period goes from 1962 to 2014, but the bulk is clearly located in the second half of the 1990s and in the 2000s.
  - AT, 1990 (Box 21)
  - Bibliographies, 1965 and undated (Box 21)
    Thematic bibliographies, either compiled by Radner or requested from him to other researchers
  - Climate Change, 2014 (Box 21)
  - Decentralization Seminar, 1998-1999; 2 folders (Box 21)
  - Economic Survival, 1995; 3 folders (Box 21)
  - Economics of IS Workshop, 2003 (Box 21)
  - Econonmics of IT Worshop, 2005 (Box 21)
  - Fisher Lecture: Optimal Capital Accumulation Under Uncertainty, 1972 and undated; 3 folders (Box 21)
  - Gaming files, 1988 (Digital-materials RL11298-SET-0001)
    77 Microsoft Print files, 0.00272 gigabytes, for game results in 1988, including round, cost, ask, transaction, price and earnings, in addition to buyer and player id and transaction rates.
  - ICIS Panel, 1997 (Box 21)
  - Information, Firms and Markets: Outsiders and Insiders (Workshop), 1997 and undated; 3 folders (Box 21)
  - Information Systems Research Seminar (ISRS), 1995-1999 and undated; 5 folders (Box 21)
  - Interdepartmental Workshop on Innovation, 2004-2005 (Box 22)
    Originally filed under "TOPICS…"
  - Interdepartmental Workshop on Deception, Corruption and Fraud, 2002-2003; 4 folders (Box 22)
  - Inderdepartmental Worshop on Information for Managerial Decision Making, 1999-2000 and undated; 2 folders (Box 22)
  - Interdepartmental Workshop on Learning from Large Data Sets (LFLDS), 2000-2001; 2 folders (Box 22)
  - Interdepartmental Workshop on Networks, 2003-2004 and undated; 5 folders (Box 22)
  - IT Workforce, 1999 (Box 22)
  - Jerusalem Summer School of Economics on "Information Economics" - Literature, 1992 (Box 22)
  - Lectures in French: Surete de fonctionnement de materiels complexes, 1962 (Box 22)
    Original file name: "Limit Laws of Reliability of Multistqge Systems"
  - Miscellaneous, 1990-1991 (Box 22)
  - Notes from AT, 1992-1993 and undated (Box 22)
    Original file name: "Prototyping"
  - Research Proposal: Economic Organization and Welfare, 1973 (Box 22)
  - Study Group on Bounded Rationality, 1998 (Box 22)
  - Study Group on Contract Theory, 2004 (Box 22)
  - Study Group on Epistemic Logic, 1994-1995 (Box 22)
  - Study Group on Returns to IT, 1995-1997; 2 folders (Box 22)
    Original file name: "IT "Productivity - Bibli"
  - Study Group on Return to Scale, 1992-1993 (Box 22)
  - Workshop on Managerial and Organizational Cognition (MOC), 1998-1999; 2 folders (Box 22)
    Original file name: "Davern Project"
- Writings by Others, 1954-2006; 5
  This series contains writings by others, i.e., mostly published papers but also working papers and Ph.D. dissertations, with or (in most cases) without notes from Radner. These documents were dispersed in all the series of the original collection, hence the constructed thematic organization is not Radner's. Accordingly, it should be noted the distinctions between "Firms and Decentralization", "Game Theory and Principal-Agent" and "Teams" is made on intuitive and semantic grounds (i.e., with respect to the words used in the titles of the papers), not on substantial theoretic grounds. It should also be noted that the dates displayed in this series are publication dates of the papers, not necessarily the dates at which Radner made notes about them or printed them.
  - With Notes from Radner: 1961-1985, 1961-1987 (Box 23)
    Contains a paper from Kenneth Arrow ("Economic Welfare and the Allocation of Resources for Invention") and a paper from Tjalling Koopmans ("Axioms for Persistent Preferences")
  - With Notes from Radner: 1989-1991 (Box 23)
    Partly from files originally named: "Dynamic Games with Delayed Information" (1991); "AT&T Transfer Pricing, 1990" (1990-1991); "Qs in PPOs" (1989-1991)
  - With Notes from Radner: 1997-2000 (Box 23)
  - Without Notes from Radner: On Corruption, 1996-2002 (Box 23)
  - Without Notes from Radner: On David Sevy's Writings, 1993-1994 (Box 23)
  - Without Notes from Radner: On Firms and Decentralization, 1954-1983 (Box 23)
  - Without Notes from Radner: On Firms and Decentralization, 1973-1995 and undated (Box 23)
    Partly from a file originally named: "Spring '96 Literature & Bibliography" (1973-1995 and undated)
  - Without Notes from Radner: On Firms and Decentralization, 1984-1986 (Box 23)
  - Without Notes from Radner: On Firms and Decentralization, 1987-2006 (Box 23)
  - Without Notes from Radner: On Game Theory and Principal-Agent, 1981-1987 and undated (Box 24)
    Partly from files originally named: "Principal/Agent Brownian Motion Model Literature" (1981-1985); "Efficient Performance in Two Agent Bargaining S.R. Williams" (Undated)
  - Without Notes from Radner: On Game Theory and Principal-Agent, 1994-1995 (Box 24)
  - Without Notes from Radner: On Game Theory and Principal-Agent, 2002-2003 (Box 24)
  - Without Notes from Radner: On Teams, 1955-1988 (Box 24)
  - Without Notes from Radner: On Various Topics, 1951-1966 (Box 24)
    Contains one old working paper by Jacob Marschak ("Economics of Leadership: Some Remarks") and another one by Leonid Hurwicz ("Comments on Statistical Decisions")
  - Without Notes from Radner: On Various Topics, 1967-1988, 1967-1988 and undated (Box 24)
    Contains an undated hand-written documents which, from its original file, seems to be from Mike Meurer
  - Without Notes from Radner: On Various Topics, 1992-2006 (Box 24)
    Partly from a file originally named: "Neural Networks" (1995-1997)